Preliminary Guide to the Yale School of Drama Production Script Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Production Scripts, 1966-2010; Series I
  - Peer Gynt, 2007-2008 (Box 97)
  - If Found, Please Return to Charles Darwin, 2007-2008 (Box 98)
  - The Covering Skyline is Nothing, 2007-2008 (Box 98)
  - Dramatis Personae, 2007-2008 (Box 98)
  - Ghost Sonata, 2007-2008 (Box 98)
  - Pericles, 2007-2008 (Box 98)
  - Romeo and Juliet, 2007-2008 (Box 98)
  - Troilus vs. Cressida, 2007-2008 (Box 99)
  - Grace, Or The Art of Climbing, 2007-2008 (Box 99)
  - Good Egg, 2007-2008 (Box 99)
  - I am a Superhero, 2007-2008 (Box 99)
  - Learning Russian, 2007-2008 (Box 99)
  - Lone Pilots of Roosevelt Field, 2007-2008 (Box 99)
  - The Art of Preservation, 2007-2008 (Box 99)
  - Man in Love, 2008-2009 (Box 100)
  - State of Affairs, 2008-2009 (Box 100)
  - Ah, Americans!, 2008-2009 (Box 100)
  - The Current War, 2008-2009 (Box 100)
  - 99 Ways to Fuck a Swan, 2008-2009 (Box 100)
  - Cygnus, 2008-2009 (Box 100)
  - Man=Man, 2008-2009 (Box 100)
  - Jellys' Last Jam, 2008-2009 (Box 101)
  - Paradise Lost, 2008-2009 (Box 101)
  - Rubles: Inspired by Chekhov, 2008-2009 (Box 101)
  - The Robbers, 2008-2009 (Box 101)
  - Hamlet, 2008-2009 (Box 101)
  - Love's Labours Lost, 2008-2009 (Box 101)
  - The Tempest, 2008-2009 (Box 102)
  - The Bedtrick, 2008-2009 (Box 102)
  - The French Play, 2008-2009 (Box 102)
  - American Catnip, 2008-2009 (Box 102)
  - The Seagull, 2009-2010 (Box 111)
  - Homebody/Kabul, 2009-2010 (Box 111)
  - Buffalo, Maine, 2009-2010 (Box 112)
  - the droll, 2009-2010 (Box 112)
  - Phedre, 2009-2010 (Box 111)
  - Every Other Hamlet in the Universe, 2009-2010 (Box 112)
  - La Ronde, 2009-2010 (Box 111)
  - The Tragedy of Macbeth, 2009-2010 (Box 111)
  - Another Quiet Evening at Home, undated (Box 112)
- Unproduced Scripts, 1961-2004
  - No Bed for Bacon: A Musical Comedy in Eighteen Scenes, 1961 (Box 113)
  - Wrong Turn on the Yellow Brick Road, 1965 (Box 113)
  - Welcome to Andromeda, 1968 (Box 113)
  - The Juncture of Billie Mapes, 1968 (Box 113)
  - Titanic, 1973 (Box 113)
  - Fire Drill, 1976 (Box 113)
  - Tonite, 1976 (Box 113)
  - On the Fritzz, 1976 (Box 113)
  - My Favorite Son, 1977 (Box 113)
  - Sister and Brother, 1977 (Box 113)
  - Returning, 1977 (Box 113)
  - Snow Queen, 1978 (Box 113)
  - Muddle, 1978 (Box 113)
  - Who They Are and How It Is With Them, 1978 (Box 113)
  - Mary Goldstein and the Author, 1978 (Box 113)
  - Bernardone, 1978 (Box 114)
  - Dancing Bears, 1979 (Box 114)
  - The Preservation of Mrs. Thacker, 1979 (Box 114)
  - A Life of Crime, 1979 (Box 114)
  - Five Short Plays, 1979 (Box 114)
  - Oedipus Again, 1979 (Box 114)
  - Rite of Passage, 1979 (Box 114)
  - Parallel Lives, 1979 (Box 114)
  - N.U.N.S., 1979 (Box 114)
  - Big Deal, 1979 (Box 115)
  - The Happy Hour (Act Two), 1979 (Box 115)
  - Season at Coole, 1979 (Box 115)
  - A Splendid Occasion in Spring, 1979 (Box 115)
  - Approaching Chimera, 1980 (Box 115)
  - Andrea Rescued, 1980 (Box 115)
  - Nijinksky, 1980 (Box 125)
    See also Nijinksky (Work in Progress) in Box 125.
  - The Two, 1981 (Box 115)
  - Whistling in the Dark, 1981 (Box 115)
  - Tears of a Summer Knife, 1981 (Box 115)
  - Colony, 1983 (Box 115)
  - Morikka, 1983 (Box 115)
  - The Pearl Story, 1983 (Box 115)
  - Love's Comedy, 1983 (Box 115)
  - Oh How We Danced, 1983 (Box 115)
  - The Unveiling, 1983 (Box 115)
  - Yanqui Holiday, 1984 (Box 116)
  - Crossroads, 1984 (Box 116)
  - The List, 1984 (Box 116)
  - Bitter Blood, 1984 (Box 116)
  - Club Versailles, 1985 (Box 116)
  - Polish Rapists, 1985 (Box 116)
  - Chariot, 1985 (Box 116)
  - Mendocino, 1985 (Box 116)
  - With More Than Voices, 1985 (Box 116)
  - Yokahama Crude, 1985 (Box 116)
  - Garden, 1985 (Box 117)
  - Baby Hades, 1985 (Box 117)
  - Becoming Legends, 1986 (Box 117)
  - Howard (screenplay), 1987 (Box 117)
  - From the Rising Sun, 1987 (Box 117)
  - Ollie!, 1988 (Box 117)
  - Beat Back the Humanist Mind Barons, 1989 (Box 117)
  - Factory, 1989 (Box 117)
    On the script, the author uses her maiden name, Lisa Wing.
  - Spring Awakening, 1989 (Box 117)
  - One True Thing, 1989 (Box 118)
  - The Ice, 1989 (Box 118)
  - The Prince of Homburg, 1990 (Box 118)
  - Cannibals, 1990 (Box 118)
  - When Black Angels Fall, 1994 (Box 118)
  - Caliban's Sister, 1994-1995 (Box 118)
  - Loving the Alien, 1994-1995 (Box 118)
  - Ululation, 1994-1995 (Box 118)
  - Dig 'n Arch, 1994-1995 (Box 118)
  - The "Far Flung", 1994-1995 (Box 118)
  - Caliban at Large, 1995-1996 (Box 118)
  - In the Swim, 1996-1997 (Box 119)
  - The Master and the Magician, 1996-1997 (Box 119)
  - A Shadowed Cross, 1996-1997 (Box 119)
  - Time Goes Crawling By, 1996-1997 (Box 119)
  - Like I Say, 1996 (Box 119)
  - The Duel, 1997-1998 (Box 119)
  - The Wit of a Sparrow, 1997-1998 (Box 119)
  - The Ballad of Armless Johnny, 1999-2000 (Box 119)
  - Melvin and the Sock Monster, 2001-2002 (Box 120)
  - Caliban, 2001-2002 (Box 120)
  - 900, 2001-2002 (Box 120)
  - Blurring Shine, 2001-2002 (Box 120)
  - Purification of the Heart: A First Step to Brahma, 2001-2002 (Box 120)
  - The Evaporation of Gene Kirchner, 2001-2002 (Box 120)
  - Aurora, 2001-2002 (Box 120)
  - Trivial Pursuit, 2001-2002 (Box 120)
  - Work in Progress, 2001-2002 (Box 120)
  - Time of No Reply, 2001-2002 (Box 120)
  - Ophelia and the Players, 2001-2002 (Box 120)
  - The Home (Act I), 2001-2002 (Box 120)
  - High, 2001-2002 (Box 121)
  - Listen, 2001-2002 (Box 121)
  - Johnny Hong Kong, 2001-2002 (Box 121)
  - One Plays, 2001-2002 (Box 121)
  - Two Play, 2001-2002 (Box 121)
  - Archie's Weird Fantasy, 2002-2003 (Box 121)
  - The Weatherman, 2002-2003 (Box 121)
  - 8 Brunches, 2002-2003 (Box 121)
  - Jacob's Room, 2002-2003 (Box 121)
  - Birthmarks, 2002-2003 (Box 121)
  - California/Berlin 1961, 2002-2003 (Box 121)
  - Absolut Hamptons, 2002-2003 (Box 121)
  - Knife, Fire, Fang, 2002-2003 (Box 121)
  - The Dark Wood, 2002 (Box 121)
  - Red Town, Utah, 2003-2004 (Box 122)
  - The Death of Milton Hubble, 2003-2004 (Box 122)
  - Worth, 2003-2004 (Box 122)
  - Sun is the New Apollo, 2003-2004 (Box 122)
  - The Sleep of Birds, 2003-2004 (Box 122)
  - Alice Eat Your Words, 2003-2004 (Box 122)
  - Apple of Discord, 2003-2004 (Box 122)
  - Home, 2003 (Box 122)
  - In Translation, 2004 (Box 122)
  - A Dream Play, undated (Box 123)
  - Face Value, undated (Box 123)
  - Mikhail and Yousuf (film treatment), undated (Box 123)
  - Private Screening, undated (Box 123)
  - The Odyssey of Homer, undated (Box 123)
  - Cheering Up Harold, undated (Box 123)
  - Keepsakes, undated (Box 123)
  - A Leap in the Dark, undated (Box 123)
  - The Bridge (Act 5), undated (Box 123)
  - Cracker, undated (Box 123)
  - The Enemy Electricians, undated (Box 123)
  - Cold Hands, Cold Hands, undated (Box 123)
  - Florida, undated (Box 123)
  - A History of the American Film (Act I only), undated (Box 123)
  - The Nature and Purpose of the Universe, undated (Box 123)
  - Hudson Local, undated (Box 124)
  - Antonio, undated (Box 124)
  - Don't Walk Around Stark Naked, undated (Box 124)
  - A New World's Record, undated (Box 124)
  - Harry the Hawk, With Hair, undated (Box 124)
  - The Brides, undated (Box 124)
  - Earth Worms, undated (Box 124)
  - The Lost Colony, undated (Box 124)
  - Waiter Station, undated (Box 124)
  - Gun, undated (Box 124)
  - You, undated (Box 124)
  - She Saw the Seizure, undated (Box 124)
  - The Uptown Flyer, undated (Box 124)
  - The Fife and the Piper, undated (Box 125)
  - Nijinksky (Work in Progress), undated (Box 125)
    See also Nijinksky (1980) in Box 125.
  - We Four, undated (Box 125)
  - The Royal Trope, undated (Box 125)
  - [Unknown Title], undated (Box 125)
  - Brave River (film treatment), undated (Box 125)
  - The Darkness of Change, undated (Box 125)
  - Happy Birthday Montpelier Pa-Zazz, undated (Box 125)